// Questions data for the trivia game
module.exports = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "In Back to the Future 1985 what speed does the DeLorean need to reach to time travel?",
        choices: ["55 mph", "66 mph", "88 mph", "77 mph"],
        answerIndex: 2, // 88 mph
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "In The Breakfast Club 1985 how many students are in detention?",
        choices: ["5", "6", "7", "8"],
        answerIndex: 0, // 5
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "Which 1984 movie features a friendly alien who wants to phone home?",
        choices: ["Short Circuit", "E.T. the Extra Terrestrial", "The Last Starfighter", "Batteries Not Included"],
        answerIndex: 1, // E.T.
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "Which 1981 movie featured Harrison Ford as Indiana Jones?",
        choices: ["Temple of Doom", "Raiders of the Lost Ark", "The Last Crusade", "Blade Runner"],
        answerIndex: 1, // Raiders of the Lost Ark
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "Which 1987 film starred Arnold Schwarzenegger as a commando hunted by an alien in the jungle?",
        choices: ["Commando", "The Terminator", "Predator", "Total Recall"],
        answerIndex: 2, // Predator
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "Which 1982 sci fi film features a policeman who hunts replicants?",
        choices: ["Tron", "Blade Runner", "Escape from New York", "WarGames"],
        answerIndex: 1, // Blade Runner
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "Which 1982 fantasy film featured a magical crystal shard and puppet characters created by Jim Henson?",
        choices: ["Labyrinth", "The NeverEnding Story", "Legend", "The Dark Crystal"],
        answerIndex: 3, // The Dark Crystal
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "Which 1986 movie is about fighter pilots and features the song Danger Zone?",
        choices: ["Iron Eagle", "Top Gun", "Flight of the Navigator", "Firefox"],
        answerIndex: 1, // Top Gun
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "Who starred as Sarah Connor in The Terminator 1984?",
        choices: ["Sigourney Weaver", "Jamie Lee Curtis", "Molly Ringwald", "Linda Hamilton"],
        answerIndex: 3, // Linda Hamilton
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "Which 1985 film follows a group of kids searching for pirate treasure?",
        choices: ["The Goonies", "Stand By Me", "Explorers", "Adventures in Babysitting"],
        answerIndex: 0, // The Goonies
    },
];